

EBIN UK
SENIOR AUDIT EXECUTIVE

Contact

Address
Ulladathara (H),
Ambikamarket P.O,
Vaikom Kottayam
686144

Phone 918086005038 E-mail

ebin.uk38@gmail.com

Key Areas Handed

Accounts, Gold, KYC

Audit

- Forex Audit
- Bank reconciliation
- Money Transfer Audit

Experienced Auditor with a strong grasp of business regulations and compliance. Known for meticulous attention to detail and organized work style. Utilizes expertise to drive operational excellence and ensure legal compliance. Dedicated to making a positive impact by identifying opportunities for improvement. Committed to delivering results that contribute to organizational success.

Work History

JUL 2022 – Present

Senior Audit Executive

KLM Axiva Finvest

Key Responsibilities

- Conduct audits for branches to ensure compliance and accuracy.
- Proactively detect and address fraud or irregularities.
- Provide timely feedback to senior management.
- Guide branch officials to prevent future irregularities.
- Handle monthly bank reconciliation tasks.
- Maintain a risk-free business environment.
- Manage NPAs and PNPA deductions with customers.
 Facilitate training for new branch and audit staff.

SEP 2018 – JUN 2022

Audit Executive

Muthoot Finance Pvt Ltd

Key responsibilities

- Conducted gold, document, KYC, and assets verification audits.
- Managed security checks, auction works, and bank account verification.

Software

- MS Office
- C
- C++
- Visual Basic
- SQL
- Java
- ASP.NET
- Photoshop

Personal Details

DOB : 09/11/1995

Marital Status: Single

Nationality : Indian

 Followed up on customer NPAs, ensuring timely resolution and minimizing financial risks.

JUL 2016 – AUG 2018

Sales Executive

Idea Cellular

- Representing the company in various exhibitions and trade fairs.
- Researching the market on a regular basis for related products.
- Arranging several effective client demonstrations.

Education

2019	MBA(Finance)
	Bharathiar University College.
2016	Bachelor of Computer Application
	Marian College Kuttikkanam
2013	Higher Secondary
	St. Michael's HSS , Kudavechoor
2011	High School Education: SSLC
	St. Michael's HSS , Kudavechoor